Amber Wilson Résumé

My name is Amber and I'm a front end engineer with a keen interest in performance, accessibility, and security. I have extensive experience in agile, version control, testing, CI/CD, and error handling. Additionally, I've worked on internal tools (TypeScript), onboarded engineers, run A/B tests, managed headless CMS requests, written middlewares for backend endpoints, overseen API creation, improved SEO, and more. In my spare time I love writing, reading, taking photos, long walks outside, meeting new people, and seeing new places!

Click to see my **personal site** (https://amberwilson.co.uk/), **GitHub** (https://github.com/ambrwlsn), **LinkedIn** (https://www.linkedin.com/in/ambrwlsn90/), **Twitter** (https://twitter.com/ambrwlsn90).

Experience

FRONT END ENGINEER, N26

Jan 2019 - Present, Berlin, Germany

- Building React UI with server-side rendering (over 3 million users).
- Using GraphQL, Apollo and Node.js middlewares for handling data.
- Writing tests with Cypress and Jest, and contributing to app releases.
- Leading development and maintenance of support website and Contentful CMS.

FRONT END DEVELOPER, EDENSPIEKERMANN

Jan 2018 - Dec 2018, Berlin, Germany

- Worked independently on a mature React application.
- Maintained a versioned design system.
- Selected and integrated tooltip library into application.
- Worked with Craft CMS.

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERN, THE UNIT

May 2017 - Dec 2017, Brighton, UK

- Contributed to an Angular application.
- Built a small PHP site.
- Participated in agile rituals and design workshops.
- Created several JavaScript (ES6) projects using APIs.

Education

MASTER OF PSYCHOLOGY

2014 - 2015, Leiden, NL